To myself, how could he possibly go in and dig through someone's freezer and it is impossible
for him to drink it all? As I proceed to the kitchen and the first thing I notice is a puddle
of pee right next to the freezer. I step over it and open the freezer. This man, coming home at
AM plastered drunk, decided it was a great idea to drink an entire bottle of someone else's vodka.
I was lost for words at this point. My uncle then grabs a mop and heads to the shower.
In curiosity I followed him only to see him using the mop like a scrubbing brush to begin to remove
the shit from his skin. We throw some clothes, my clothes mind you, onto him and then carry him
downstairs to the car. As I take him to the airport, my aunt and uncle tackle the cleaning
of the house. As I pulled up to the airport, I remember exactly his face as I was leaning over
to open the passenger side door. Pure misery as he was half asleep and still drunk as you can
imagine. I open the door and push him out, pull back in the passenger door and drive off. When I
return to the apartment, I see the entire couch already on the sidewalk to be collected by the
rubbish truck. My aunt at this point did a great job at mopping and sanitizing the floor. I ask my
uncle how in the hell did you come to find him like this did you happen to wake up early and
just see him like fish tells me here is the best part that his twins usually wake up early and
watch cartoons on a morning they are at the age where they can navigate themselves out of their
beds and turn on the tv to not disturb them and the kids innocently walking in the living room
that morning were the first to see and immediately ran into their room and said mommy daddy there is
a naked man on the coach hey then flew out of bed in confusion and ran out to find him this way
passed out naked and with porn showing on the tv the porn might explain why he decided to get
naked however the belt still on thing baffles me to this day to wrap up the story i never saw jc
again after that have no clue if he ever knew what happened he did in fact purchase the
beeline from my boss and we will never know if guilt made him buy it